During the Sunday service at the SCOAN, Prophet TB Joshua
begins to move in the midst of the congregation under the check and conduct of the holy spirits.
The results are clear... healing and deliverance in the name of Jesus Christ.
Amidst the crowd is this young lady who falls violently to the ground as she receives prayer.
The evil spirit that was lurking in her has been exposed by the power of God.
Let's watch what happens next.
So she's free from the spirit of man inside her.
Set free in Jesus' Name
Thank you Jesus! Thank you Jesus!
Testimony Time
My name is Lisa Venant, I'm twenty-three years of age.
The woman standing beside me is my mother. I am from Tanzania.
Last Sunday Man of God delivered me from the spirit of man.
It has been tormenting me since I'm 10 years old. I was in grade 3 by then.
It has lived inside me for 13 years.
This spirit got into me through dreams. I have been dreaming I'm sleeping with a woman.
It has been living in me and whenever I used to wake up in the morning I used to have that desire
of sleeping with a woman.
So
Any woman who used to come in front of me I used to approach a woman by the time I was in grade 3.
No woman ever denied. They used to accept me.
It lived in me till I got in secondary
In secondary, I was in a boarding school. Everything that I'm saying my mum doesn't know about it.
So...
When I was in secondary school, we had two preps we had morning preps and night preps.
During morning preps, whenever they announced that we had to go to the classes to study.
I used to stay in the dormitory, sleeping with a woman.
Evening and morning preps I used to do the same. So by day I used to sleep with two..
I mean with three or four women per day.
So that spirit lived in me till I got to University. I met this woman. She approached me. I never knew she was
married. We dated and we used to sleep together. We had a relationship.
Since then, I never knew till the husband called me and wanted me to stay away from his wife.
Of which I did...
but at that instant
He called my mom
I don't know how he got the number and he told my mom to warn me to stay away from his wife. I
I remember that day my mom called me and asked me about it
But I never accepted it and I denied that it was true.
I used to dress like a man, talk like a man, behave like a man. I used to have that desire of having..sleeping
with women any woman who would just pass by. I had that spirit pushing me whenever I see a woman
I could never just let her pass me by. So I just found myself approaching them.
But since I've been delivered, I'm sleeping well. I don't have that desire for women anymore.
Shall we put our hands together for our Lord Jesus
Yes sister, before you tell us how God Almighty delivered you from that spirit, can you share with us?
Do you have any experience in the past that you will never forget while you were tormented by this demon
who caused you to have desire for women like you
Yes, I remember there was a day..I'm talking about the past. I used to have this woman I used to date..
we went to a hotel and I never knew the receptionist had called the police and they came to our room
That was the instant. I never forget
Have you have not make any attempt to stop on your own since you knew that this was a spirit that was
tormenting you that you could not control?
Did you try by yourself to stop it?
Yes. Yes
I went through different churches to seek for my deliverance
But because that spirit inside me was very strong
Whenever I stayed for that deliverance, the more I seeked for it
the more the spirit is pushing me and taking me into that thing that has been tormenting me the spirit of man.
And now can you share with us how you finally came to the synagogue Church?
After my mom realized that that spirit had been tormenting me, she begged me to come to the SCOAN.
Because of that spirit I used to deny it before but because of what I've been going through how my life
has changed, so I decided to accept my mom's offer and I said, "Okay mom, now it's time to go to the SCOAN."
to seek for my mercy and my deliverance.
Last week as you saw on the television..
Man of God touched me.
He delivered me from the spirit of man that had been tormenting me for 13 years.
Right now, I thank God I'm free and I give God the glory
Shall we put our hands together for our Lord Jesus once again.
I give God the glory. I never used to put on earrings in my life. I never used to dress like a lady
but now I can see changes in me..
Once again, shall we put our hands together for how Lord Jesus
What God Almighty has done for you, before we listen to your mother, what advice can you give our youth?
My friends..
even my brothers and sisters we were inside this church right now
The advice that I want to give you
Please, please, please, I beg..if.. you have the same spirit that has been tormenting me...please seek for God.
Talk to your parents.
Explain to them what you feel. What you always dream; the bad dreams that you always have.
So that they can seek for help. This spirit is a very bad spirit. It confuses you.
You lose your career. You cannot focus. It was very hard on me.
So please if you have this spirit, just talk to your parents, seek for God's help and he will help you
My parents if you have your children at home...
As I say, this spirit has been tormenting me for 10 years
You might think your child is a little kid by 8 or 9 or 10. But by that age, that´s the age that devil is very close
to the kids and he's tormenting them
with different spirits. So please try and look after your kids. Focus on them.
Especially those who are in bording schools, because there is a different type of life there.
You meet different people different characters. So please whenever they come to holiday
get close to your kids and that will help you to know if it has any problem that is tormenting him or her.
Once again, let us put a hands together for our Lord Jesus.
Yes, we give all the glory to God and we are very blessed by your advice and we believe that viewers all around the
world are listening to your advice parents are listening guidance are listening and I believe that the Lord will
guide them to be able to look after their children and train them in the way of the Lord in Jesus name.
My name is Flora Bina Moon.
I came from Tanzania. The lady beside me is my daughter.
The problem that brought us here to the SCOAN
is because of that spirit of man that has been tormenting my daughter.
I thank God last Sunday, she got her deliverance.
The other thing she has confessed here, I didn't know that for almost ten years...
until that man called me and told me that I tell my daughter to stay away from his wife. I was so confused.
I was shocked. I called my daughter. I asked her she denied it.
After one week, she called me. She said: "Mom, I'm sorry. I've been that spirit for a long time."
She started confessing to me.
After her deliverance. What are the changes as a mother that you have noticed?
I've seen a lot of changes: She sleeps well.. Before, she didn't sleep. She.. she..
At night, she used to chat till the morning on the phone.
She walked like a man. She talked like a man.
But since last Sunday, she talked like a lady, she´s more affectionate.
I thank God.
You said she would normally chat on her phone in the past.
Yes.
But now?
Now she's not chatting anymore.
Now, with all you have heard from your daughter. What advice would you like to give to the parents.
I advise all parents, all over the world that they watch their kids and see what they are doing and seek God.
Once again, shall we put our hands together for our Lord Jesus!
Deliverance Testimony
Yes, because of the language barrier, her mommy is giving advice for parents all around the world
So, please look after their children
Do you not say your children must get to a certain age before you watch over them?
But at a young age like our sister said of nine years you don't even think you should look after your children
or that Satan will not take them away from you. I will believe that the same God who has restored our sister
that has delivered her from the spirit of man will also deliver those who were listening to her right now,
those who have similar problem in Jesus name.
After her dramatic deliverance and inspiring testimony, it is time for Lisa Vilant to return to her homeland
of Tanzania
Lisa is eager for the very first time in her life to actually wear female clothing.
Taken into a shop, she begins to choose in sizes of various items of female clothing
Something she had never done before in her life.
Truly he has been returned to the original position in which God created her: a female.
As Prophet TB Joshua says:
"Faith is the transformative power of the universe; the power of change...
from where you are, to where God wants you to be."
Lisa Venant & Mother
Deliverance Testimony
Beautifully dressed in a skirt and blouse.
Lisa Venant & Mother
Deliverance Testimony
Lisa is about to embark on her journey back to Tanzania with her mother.
Lisa Venant & Mother
Deliverance Testimony
A smile on the face says it all.
She is free indeed. And the spirit of man has gone forever.
Indeed what a God we have to worship!
What a Son we have to praise and what a future lies before us!
Thank you, Jesus Christ!
TT: Jacqueline Margaret 17/12/18